If I had to forex sales in a business
and I wasn't allowed to change the ads,
I wasn't allowed to change the sales script,
I wasn't allowed to change the offer,
there's one thing that just about every business can do
that they aren't doing because it's hard,
which is you can respond to leads
the moment they opt in, and hold on.
So HubSpot did a study and tracked
how your response time after lead opts in
affects your actual getting in touch with them
and talking to them.
And so they did a group A version
where they contacted them 30 minutes after opting in,
and then group B, five minutes after they opted in,
group B was 100 times, 100 times,
more likely to contact the lead.
And so that is how you increase revenue by forex
is that you make the leads that you have
which you currently think are shit actually great
because you give yourself a real shot at talking to them
because the reality is that someone has a huge motivation
for a tiny period of time,
and we need to be there in that moment.